# ARTUR BAGDASARIANI

## **SUMMARY**

Strong knowledge of C# fundamentals, OOP principles, HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Seeking an entry level web developer position. Previously, two year practical experience gained in financial industry, in top audit firms. Expertise in preparing financial statements and conducting ratio analysis of real-world businesses.

### SKILLS

**PROGRAMMING:** HTML, CSS, Javascript, C#, Python, T-SQL **LANGUAGES:** Georgian, Russian, English, Armenian, Chinese

### COURSES

ASP.NET Core Developer - ITVDN

Aug. 2020 - Current

Learning C# fundamentals, OOP principles, T-SQL, LINQ, Entity Framework Core, ASP.NET Core

The Web Developer Bootcamp - Udemy

Oct. 2020 - Nov. 2020

Learnt fundamentals of web development, in particular advanced HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Responsive Web Design Certification - freeCodeCamp

Sept. 2020 - Oct. 2020

Learnt basic HTML, CSS and responsive web design principles

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures - freeCodeCamp

Sept. 2020 - Oct. 2020

Learnt to assign variables, arrays, create functions, applied that in multiple algorithm creation challenges in JavaScript.

### **PROJECTS**

#### Survey form **Z**

Responsive web page, where user should fill survey

#### To-do list ☑

To-do list with quite nice interface using JavaScript and jQuery

### Travel agency ∠

A responsive one-page website with modern design for travel agency

#### **Calculator Z**

Windows forms application written on C#

### Memory game ♂

Game where user should memorize allocation of same picture in order to win

### **EMPLOYMENT**

KPMG, Auditor, Tbilisi, Georgia

Aug. 2019 - Oct. 2020

• Performed audit procedures during projects within different teams. Industry background: banking, retailing, mining, realestate etc.

Grant Thornton, Business Process Analyst, Tbilisi, Georgia

Mar. 2019 - July 2019

• Performed outsourcing of financial accounting services to firms specializing in logistics, hospitality and IT industries

### **EDUCATION**

#### **International Black Sea University**

2016 - 2020

Bachelor of Business and Technologies GPA 93%

### **SolBridge International School of Business**

2017 - 2018

Exchange program in South Korea

### **AWARDS**

Silver Medal, Ministry of Education and Science of Georgia

June 2016